<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<informationPages>
  <informationPage oid="1237324580955">
    <codePage>aboutus</codePage>
    <title>About Us</title>
    <page>&lt;p&gt;Le projet de &lt;a class="wiki_link" href="https://www.assembla.com/wiki/show/Team_FCP/TeamFCP"&gt;TeamFCP&lt;/a&gt; cette session est &lt;a class="wiki_link" href="https://www.assembla.com/wiki/show/Team_FCP/TwoADW"&gt;TwoADW&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="wiki_link" href="https://www.assembla.com/wiki/show/Team_FCP/TwoADW"&gt;TwoADW&lt;/a&gt; est un site web qui permet &amp;agrave; des petites entreprises n'ayant pas les ressources n&amp;eacute;cessaire pour d&amp;eacute;velopper leur propre site web transactionnel, d'avoir une solution web facile d'utilisation et peu dispendieuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Le site web vient avec un "back office" l&amp;eacute;ger qui permet &amp;agrave; l'entreprise de modifier le site &amp;agrave; son image (banni&amp;egrave;re, description, titre...) et d'ajouter ses propres cat&amp;eacute;gories de produits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Le but du projet est de rendre la gestion du site web le plus simple possible pour les utilisateurs avec un degr&amp;eacute; de connaissance informatique minimale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(to translate)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pascal Daneault&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mahamadou Traore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cyril Janody &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dzenan Ridjanovic&lt;small&gt; (Teacher)&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(to finish)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</page>
    <published>true</published>
  </informationPage>
  <informationPage oid="1237583106075">
    <codePage>contact</codePage>
    <title>Contact Us</title>
    <page>&lt;p&gt;For contact, please use the our Assembla web space : &lt;a href="https://www.assembla.com/wiki/show/Team_FCP" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.assembla.com/wiki/show/Team_FCP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</page>
    <published>true</published>
  </informationPage>
  <informationPage oid="1237583132607">
    <codePage>privacy</codePage>
    <title>Privacy Policy</title>
    <page>&lt;h3&gt;Sample privacy policy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This privacy policy sets out how [business name] uses and protects any information that you give [business name] when you use this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[business name] is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[business name] may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from [date].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What we collect&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may collect the following information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;name and job title&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;contact information including email address&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What we do with the information we gather&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Internal record keeping.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;We may use the information to improve our products and services.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Links to other websites&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Controlling your personal information&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [email address]&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [address].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.&lt;/p&gt;</page>
    <published>true</published>
  </informationPage>
  <informationPage oid="1237583155958">
    <codePage>terms</codePage>
    <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
    <page>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern [business name]'s relationship with you in relation to this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The term '[business name]' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is [address]. Our company registration number is [company registration number and place of registration]. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without [business name]'s prior written consent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of England, Scotland and Wales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Sample internet copyright notice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website and its content is copyright of [business name] - &amp;copy; [business name] [year]. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;you may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;div&gt;you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.&lt;/p&gt;</page>
    <published>true</published>
  </informationPage>
  <informationPage oid="1238529027155">
    <codePage>help</codePage>
    <title>Help</title>
    <page>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to get help?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FAQ section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read the Q&amp;amp;A from the items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</page>
    <published>true</published>
  </informationPage>
</informationPages>
